### **SEAN HEGARTY**

### INTEGRATED ARTWORKER

I've spent the past 15 years helping clients build strong, clear and consistent visual communications. My work displays a proven track record of inventive and compelling creative work across print and digital mediums.

During these challenging times, I'm looking to build strong relationships with Creative Directors, Designers and Account Managers to creat compelling brands and a strong identity for companies.

I work with clients in creating video content posted on Instagram as part of integrated marketing campaigns.

I've also spent time managing a studio of a agency, which has given me an insight into how a successful project should move through an agency from conception to implementation.

### **CONTACT**

07855 456521

### **CAREER**

### Freelance Integrated Artworker (June 2013 - Present)

- > Worked for a range of production and creative agencies, global corporate clients, start ups, charities and media companies, working on a vast amount of brands at various levels across all mediums. The clients I've recently worked with are listed below:
- Identity-Design (March & August 2020). Assisted in the marketing of the Whitmore Collection residential development and the branding of the CocaWorks marketing suite in York
- > **The Honest Brand** (March 2020). Helped with implementing the branding for Boost Mobiles
- > **Rover Inc** (Febuary/March 2020). Creating web banners as part of an integrated European-wide marketing campaign targeting dog owners
- > **Splash Worldwide** (January/February 2020). Worked as part of a wider team, implementing the roll-out of the new Investec branding
- > **Canary Wharf Group** (February 2018 September 2019). Worked for the Residential, Retail and Events teams on a wide variety of print and digital projects, from the kick-off meeting through to final delivery
- Other clients I've worked for in chronological order include Digitas, NKD Learning, Suburbia, Audio Network Limited, Effection, Me&Dave, Chelsea Football Club, Axa Insurance, Comic Relief, Sectorlight, Quill Content, Mindshare, Health Circle, Wallace Health, Digitas Health Lifebrands, Agora Health, Lambert Smith Hampton, Saatchi Health, Conrad Design Group, Lebara, Architas, Jones Lang LaSalle, Anderson Norton Design, Ampersand, FKA Studios, Lockton Insurance, Adstream, M&G Investments, Savills, Audience Media, The Football Association, G4S, Avery Dennison, Publicis Life Brands, BlackRock, Lusso, Initial, Law Creative and BrocklebankPenn

### Head of Studio at Gungho Design (July 2010 – May 2013)

- > Managing 5 designers and a team of freelancers
- > Focus on designing bid documents and interactive presentations
- > Communicating a clear vision to the design team
- > Project managing multiple complex projects

#### **Artworker** at **UBS Global Asset Management** (August 2008 – July 2010)

- > Produced artwork for the Business Development Team
- > Created regular financial and corporate reports
- > Worked under pressure to meet a succession of client deadlines

### Pitch Executive at CB Richard Ellis (August 2007 – August 2008)

- > Provided design support for the Pitch & Proposal Team
- > Prepared presentations for client pitches, such as interactive presentations, brochures, banners and moodboards
- > Project managed and designed large strategic proposal documents

### **TESTIMONIALS**

It was an absolute pleasure to have Sean work as part of our team over the last 18 months. Sean has a can-do attitude and demonstrated a highly considered and thoughtful approach to all tasks undertaken. He is extremely professional, has very strong technical skills and made positive and valuable contributions to each project he worked on. Sean will be a very valuable asset to any company that employs him in the future.

Manuela Zwingmann Wood Group Marketing Manager (Brand & Residential) at Canary Wharf Group September 2019

Sean is a real pleasure to work with. Focused, self-motivated, pragmatic and skilled, he can always be trusted to 'just get it done' when you need it. As good alone as he is fitting into a well-established team, Sean is committed and adaptable across media old and new – what's more he's also a really nice guy.

# **Tom Malt**Creative Services Director at BlackRock *August 2015*

### **CAREER** (continued)

## **Design Specialist** at **Deutsche Bank** (February 2001 – August 2007)

- > Designed and formatted bespoke and branded printed documents and on-screen presentations
- > Developed an understanding of colour management, styles, layers, grids, and master pages

### **Various roles**

(1995 - 2001)

Employers included IPC Media, World Soccer 6ix's, and Marylebone Cricket Club

### **ATTRIBUTES**

### > Good eye for layout, with good retouching and visualising ability

- > Successfully delivered consistent brand and campaign roll-out
- > Collaborative skills to work with internal and external clients
- > Combine creative flair with technical skill to produce the highest quality artworks and assets
- > Methodical approach to archiving images and artwork
- > Adaptable self-starter who can hit the ground running

### **SKILLS**

- > Advanced knowledge of Indesign, Photoshop, Illustrator and Acrobat
- Produced social media videos and 2D animations using After Effects and Premier Pro
- > Knowledge of HTML, CSS (SASS) and basic JavaScript. Familiar with using Gulp, Node JS and Bootstrap in building websites
- Delivery of digital upload, download and file transfer processes
- > Microsoft Office proficiency
- > Typing (60wpm)

### **EDUCATION**

BA Joint – Honours Degree in History & Politics (2:1) Leicester University (1989 – 1992)

### **INTERESTS**

Design, travelling, eating out, photography, cycling, running, coding, exploring London.